<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<android.support.constraint.ConstraintLayout
    xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent">

    <Button
        android:id="@+id/blog_details_bt_comment"
        android:layout_width="0dp"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:background="#000000"
        android:text="Leave Comment"
        android:textColor="#ffffff"
        app:layout_constraintBottom_toBottomOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent" />

    <ScrollView
        android:id="@+id/blog_details_sv_scroller"
        android:layout_width="0dp"
        android:layout_height="0dp"
        app:layout_constraintBottom_toTopOf="@+id/blog_details_bt_comment"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent">

        <android.support.constraint.ConstraintLayout
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="match_parent">

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/blog_details_tv_title"
                android:layout_width="0dp"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:layout_marginEnd="8dp"
                android:layout_marginStart="8dp"
                android:layout_marginTop="16dp"
                android:text="This is the title of the blog"
                android:textColor="#000000"
                android:textSize="20sp"
                android:textStyle="bold"
                app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
                app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
                app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent" />

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/textView16"
                android:layout_width="0dp"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:layout_marginEnd="8dp"
                android:layout_marginStart="8dp"
                android:layout_marginTop="8dp"
                android:lineSpacingExtra="3sp"
                android:text="Around 75% of college students, at some point, work in an internship. These experiences can be tremendously valuable, providing young workers the opportunity to build skills for their resumes and meet people who are working in their preferred industry. Increasingly, they are the likeliest route to full time employment and are even offered year-round rather than only during summer months. But they can also be difficult adjustments for young people who have little to no experience in professional offices. It can be hard for someone to stand out and make the right impression during a 1-3 month stint spent adapting to such a new environment.  How can interns learn what they need to know, impress those they work for, and secure a job recommendation or full-time offer in such a brief period of time. This advice won't cover everything, but it does offer a starting point for interns.  Start with relentless punctuality. Show up on time (or early) in the morning, arrive for meetings before they begin, and complete tasks by their deadlines. When I asked professional contacts for their advice to interns, they consistently listed punctuality as a critical success factor. Ryan, an executive in a municipal government, says, &quot;Always be on time. Summer internships are for a short, defined period of time, so give it 100%. Be willing to get to the office early and stay late.&quot; As an intern, you are both a guest in a new environment and a colleague on whom others must rely - make sure that you respect those colleagues by being on time.  Complete each task with excellence. Whether an assignment is mundane or exotic, pursue it with relentless drive and a determination to exceed. If you're asked to make coffee, make the best coffee your colleagues have ever had. If you're asked to make an Excel model, over-invest your time and effort in assuring it is right, aesthetically appealing, and thorough. Amy, a food and beverage executive puts it this way, &quot;Finish the assignment or project with excellence - anything else you do is bonus, but please start with the assignment given.&quot; Even if the project seems small or unimportant, do not give in to the temptation to complete it with anything less than your best, and don't decline a project just because it doesn't interest you. Katie, a tech industry executive cautions to &quot;[never] say no to small opportunities because [they don't] fit your idea of work.&quot; Repeated, enthusiastic, and excellent delivery of assigned tasks is the building block upon which everything else in your internship will rest.  Take on more work - without being asked. Use excess time to take on new and important work, assignments others don't want, or projects that are needed but not yet clearly defined. A nonprofit healthcare executive counsels, &quot;When you see something you can do, do it.&quot; I still remember the names of interns I've worked with who never let themselves sit idle and took on new projects with little or no guidance. Gary, a finance executive, told me, &quot;Sitting at the desk checking your most recent Twitter feed while you wait for someone to give you something to do is one of the best ways to not get an invite back.&quot; Deliver what no one is expecting - or what no one else is willing to do - and you'll not only be appreciated, but remembered."
                android:textAlignment="viewStart"
                android:textAllCaps="false"
                android:textColor="#000000"
                app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
                app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
                app:layout_constraintTop_toBottomOf="@+id/blog_details_tv_title" />

        </android.support.constraint.ConstraintLayout>
    </ScrollView>

    <com.makeramen.roundedimageview.RoundedImageView
        android:id="@+id/blog_details_riv_profiledp"
        android:layout_width="40dp"
        android:layout_height="40dp"
        android:layout_marginBottom="16dp"
        android:layout_marginRight="16dp"
        android:clickable="true"
        android:elevation="10dp"
        android:scaleType="centerCrop"
        android:src="@drawable/china_three"
        app:layout_constraintBottom_toTopOf="@id/blog_details_bt_comment"
        app:layout_constraintRight_toRightOf="parent"
        app:riv_corner_radius="20dp"
        app:srcCompat="@drawable/china_two" />

</android.support.constraint.ConstraintLayout>